Samarcand Manor School Records SR.5899
State Archives of North Carolina
- Administrative Binders, 1935 - 1944; SR.5899.9; Department of Public Safety
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 7, 1937; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 7)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 8, 1938; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 8)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 9, 1938-1944; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 9)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 10, 1939; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 10)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 11, 1939-1940; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 11)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 12, 1940-1941; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 12)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 13, 1941; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 13)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 14, 1941; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 14)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 15, 1941-1944; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 15)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 16, 1936-1943; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 16)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 17, 1943; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 17)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Page 18, 1943; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Page 18)
  - Administrative Binder 1: Loose Back Materials, 1944; SR.5899.008; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 1: Loose Back Materials)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Loose Front Materials, 1941-1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Loose Front Materials)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 1, 1944; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 1)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Pages 2-4, 1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Pages 2-4)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 5, 1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 5)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 6, 1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 6)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 7, 1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 7)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 8, 1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 8)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 9, 1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 9)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 10, 1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 10)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 11, 1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 11)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 12, undated; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 12)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 13, 1941-1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 13)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 14, 1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 14)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 15, 1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 15)
  - Administrative Binder 2: Page 16, 1943; SR.5899.009; Department of Public Safety (Folder Administrative Binder 2: Page 16)
- Restricted Records, 1915 - 2011; SR.5899.10; Department of Crime Control and Public Safety
  Access Restrictions
  This record group contains records restricted under public records law, General Statute 7B-3100. Records that expose the identity of juvenile offenders are restricted in access to the juvenile, their attorney, parent or guardian or by order of the court.
  Where possible, redacted copies of these records have been made available and are denoted as such with "Contains redacted copies of records restricted under GS 7B-3100" on the folder.
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor School Records: Manuscript Originals, 1915-2011; SR.5899.011; Department of Crime Control and Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor School Records: Manuscript Originals, 1915-2011; SR.5899.012; Department of Crime Control and Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor School Records: Photographs, 1915-2011; SR.5899.013; Department of Crime Control and Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor School Records: Photographs, 1915-2011; SR.5899.014; Department of Crime Control and Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Gift Log, 1919-1920; SR.5899.015; Department of Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Gift Log, 1932-1938; SR.5899.016; Department of Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Gift Log, 1938-1942; SR.5899.017; Department of Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Gift Log, 1942-1943; SR.5899.018; Department of Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Gift Log, 1943-1944; SR.5899.019; Department of Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Gift Log, 1944-1945; SR.5899.020; Department of Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Scrapbook, circa 1920s - crica 1940s; SR.5899.021; Department of Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Scrapbook, circa 1920s - crica 1940s; SR.5899.022; Department of Crime Control and Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Scrapbook, circa 1920s - crica 1940s; SR.5899.023; Department of Crime Control and Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Scrapbook, circa 1920s - crica 1940s; SR.5899.024; Department of Crime Control and Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Scrapbook, circa 1920s - crica 1940s; SR.5899.025; Department of Crime Control and Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Scrapbook, circa 1920s - crica 1940s; SR.5899.026; Department of Crime Control and Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Visitors Log, 1959-1962; SR.5899.027; Department of Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Oversize Photos, 1926; SR.5988.028; Department of Public Safety
  - RESTRICTED Samarcand Manor Blueprints, 1920 - 2011; SR.5899.029; Department of Crime Control and Public Safety